<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SUPERHEROES</string>


    <string name="superman">Superman possesses the powers of flight, superhuman
        strength, x-ray vision, heat vision, cold breath, super-speed, enhanced hearing,
        and nigh-invulnerability. While Superman is immensely strong both in terms of
        muscle power and ability to take physical punishment, he is not all-powerful.
    </string>


    <string name="batman">Genius-level intellect Expert detective Master martial
        artist and hand-to-hand combatant Master tactician,
        strategist, and field commander Peak human physical
        and mental condition Utilizes high-tech equipment and weapons
    </string>


    <string name="spiderman">Spider-Mans Powers and Abilities: Superhuman strength, agility,
        endurance, ability to stick to and climb walls and other surfaces,
        uses self-designed web-shooters allowing him to fire and swing from
        sticky webs, special "Spider-Sense" warns of incoming danger,
        genius intellect specializing in chemistry and invention.
    </string>


    <string name="hulk">During the experimental detonation of a gamma bomb,
        scientist Robert Bruce Banner saves teenager Rick Jones who has
        driven onto the testing field; Banner pushes Jones into a trench
        to save him, but is hit with the blast, absorbing massive amounts
        of gamma radiation. He awakens later seemingly unscathed, but
        that night transforms into a lumbering grey form.
        A pursuing soldier dubs the creature a "hulk".
    </string>


    <string name="flash">Because he is a speedster, his power
        consists mainly of superhuman speed. Various other effects
        are also attributed to his ability to control the slowness
        of molecular vibrations, including his ability to vibrate
        at speed to pass through objects.
    </string>
    <string name="rocket">Master tactician and field commander
        Skilled marksman and hand-to-hand combatant Genius-level
        intellect Accomplished starship aviator Normal-physical
        attributes of an Earth raccoon

    </string>
    <string name="groot">Groots abilities are all-natural and stem
        from the dendronic wood that makes up his entire body.
        The extraterrestrial bark he was born with makes him
        invulnerable to most projectiles and even fire.
        He can control all plant life via psychokinesis,
        absorbing it into his body and making himself stronger.
    </string>
    <string name="ironman">Genius level intellect Proficient
        scientist and engineer Powered armor suit: Superhuman
        strength, speed, durability, agility, reflexes,
        and senses Supersonic flight Energy repulsor and missile
        projection Regenerative life support
    </string>
</resources>